Remiller, I'm gonna put out a story.
A song about liking yourself, liking yourself, liking yourself
A song to be
Let me shout
Let me cry
I don't know
You'll love you, love you, love you
Remember me
You already have a big event for Christmas this year, don't you?
Oh, it's a big one
First round of R1
Not that one.
Speaking of December 24th this year...
It's Ralph Ruff's turd one-man show!
No, so it'll be great.
This time, the venue is the biggest ever!
TFT Hall with a capacity of 1000 people!
Isn't 1,000 people a huge capacity?
How about this?
1000 people for a one-man turd show?
Well, it's early.
It's not early.
Unless you're a major idol who's been doing this for a long time.
When you're just starting out, it's fast.
That's why we've prepared this plan to make this important event more exciting.
I've prepared this plan for you.
What you want to do at the one-man turd presentation partyTurd One-Man What You Want to Do Presenter Meeting
Yay!
So, let's say last time.
Saito's
Contrast
Yes, he wanted to do a contraption.
So we did a skit, and it was a lot of fun.
I was so happy!
We were able to see it, too, and it was really funny.
It was really funny.
Really?
It was long.
Yes, it was.
Was it a little bit?
Yeah, it was a little bit.
We were at it for about 20 minutes.
Twenty minutes.
Just a little bit.
I did it for about 20 minutes.
I did about 20 minutes.
Now then, let's hear a little bit about it, shall we?
Yes, Fujisaki.
Yes, sir.
Boom.
No answer.
I borrowed a piece of glitter tape and popped it on.
Then why?And why?
Oh, I'm just adding that we'd like to have a show where people can leave at 10:00.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
It's not a good time.
Punctual?
It's Christmas Eve.
Oh, ho, ho, ho.
I have to go to bed early.
Oh, why?
I have to wait for Santa.
Oh, that's terrible.
That's nasty.
That's harsh.
We're on the offensive this year.
We're at a crossroads.
It might be the last one.
I don't know.
I guess it's safe to say you already know the structure.
Who is? I mean...
Who's Santa Claus? You know, there's a structure.
I've seen it before.
Oops.
You're a hard woman to please.
I used to sleep in my dad's room.
I was sleeping in my dad's room.
I just...
I kind of woke up.
And there was this invisible Santa Claus.
I took a look at him.
Listen to me.Listen to me.
Exactly the same?
Well, I took a peek at the place like this.
And there's a forest of animals popping up.
It's exactly the same.
Transparent, transparent.
Transparent, transparent, transparent Santa Claus clothes.
And right here, buried in the bed...
Same? Together?
Together?
Let's not do this again.
I'm scared.
Let's not do this, I'm scared.
I'm afraid of the show.
I know an idol who can see a transparent, transparent Santa Claus
I'm scared
I've never done this before, and no matter what I said, you didn't believe me... for a long time.
But there were two of them.
They're in Fukuoka and Chiba.
I don't mind talking about that.
Okay, Takanashi.
Let me tell you about a project I'd like to do.
I'm going to fulfill everyone's request.
I'll call for applications in advance.
That's right.
And what do you usually hear at these photo sessions?
Yes.
"I'd like to see the unit's song.
I see.Oh, I see.
And since it's Christmas, you want him to wear a Santa costume.
I see.
I'm hoping we can give away some of the items that we collected from the public.
This seems like it would be easy to realize.
It's a good idea.
I'd like to hear about it.
I'd like to hear it.
That's good.
Then, Nagamatsu...
I'll be the guest speaker, and I'll be the signing ball.
Yes.
I usually go to live shows of idols.
Yes, yes...
And of course I go to the big stages too.
Yes.
I also go to places where there are no steps.
But...
And then you can't really see them.
I see.
Sometimes you can only see about the same distance as your head.
Well, go down the aisle to the customer's place.
Yeah.
It makes me so happy when they come.
It's better to come than not to come at all.
Just seeing you up close makes all the difference in the sense of satisfaction. Well, you know, just to be able to see them up close makes all the difference in the sense of satisfaction.
And also, everyone wants an autographed ball as a present for Christmas.
Hee...
I wanted to make it possible for people who can't see in the back to enjoy the show, so I put this out.
It's a sense of togetherness, of everyone having fun together.
Yeah, that's right.
It's the person who runs the event.
But he really has some opinions.
You're really solid.
This place is amazing.
Okay, Yoshimura.
Yes, I'm talking about my sense of togetherness.
Let's make a music video together.
Oh, you mean on the spot?
I'm thinking of a live Christmas concert, where everyone has a selfie stick...
Right.
And then some of us would take pictures from the stage, and some of us would go down to the audience and take pictures, and then we'd edit it all together and make a music video.
That would be great!
Yeah, but that's just for that one time only, isn't it?
I thought it would be fun to make a music video of the live performance.
People who were at the show could look back and enjoy it.
That would be great.
That's great.
It's a little blurry.
That's right.
I think it's better to take it all seriously.
The challenge equipment is getting better.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Is this thing okay?
Yes, I'm fine.Yes, sir.
Is it hard to open?
Not at all.
Okay, Saito.
I've been active since March.
As I got to know my fans.
I wanted to do something like this.
That's the Bird Man Contest.
That?
It's right in the middle.
In the Avian Contest, you make a bird fly.
But you can't do that live.
So we had a competition to see who could be the best bird.
We all dress up as a bird and do a bird model.
And then they decide who gets to be the best.
The ones who didn't make it...
The ones who didn't make it will be left behind.
The losers?
The losers.
The ones who are good enough to be birds.
It's the same contest as the Brickyard Championship.
There's a justice in the Brick Championships, right?
Idols do it.
Birds don't have to.
Birds do.
Have you ever seen an idol become a bird and sell well?
But you want to show a new side of yourself.
That's how they sell, right?
It sold as a bird. Sold for a bird.
Just a touch?
Touch of the bird
The bird at the beginning.
Why not?
We can do it at the beginning.
With the bird at the beginning?
Rolling.
Roll, roll, roll, roll, roll, roll.
Riddle me this.
Well, it would be at the beginning.
But you're going to keep entering with this and then you're not going to enter
I mean, you can't enter that song until it's over.
Well, who was that pass/fail?
But the people watching, well, the adults...
You're going to involve adults in this?
There's not a single adult who can judge a bird right now.
It's hard to do that.
I only have Genichi Niinuma.
You're right
There's no Shinnuma Genichi
Yes, then Hibino
Hibino presents
Let's make Rachlaff our girlfriend... the Christmas version
What's that?
This is from the last Bricko project.
We all said cute lines and got embarrassed.
It was so cute when they said cute lines and got embarrassed, wasn't it?
That's what I want to do.
That's what I'm going to do. That's what we're going to do.
You mean Hibino's going to say his lines?
Some of the guys were running.
I found him.
The Hibino police got it right.
But I thought it was funny too.
You know what?
You're going to make a comedy out of that? Brikkov? You're going to make a comedy?
It's about a very scary boss.
Brikkov.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
You've got "Blikkopf".
Brikkov's comedy.
That sounds fun.
I'm going to teach it to him.
I'll teach him.
Go on, then.
Okay, Natsume.
I want to have a Christmas party.
That's...
Turn it around.
What are you going to do for Christmas?
I want to have a bird contest.
I want to do that.
Are you entering the bird contest?
Two.
Oh, wow.
That's great.
So you have two confirmed?
I thought we had two confirmed. I'm glad you decided on two people.
I want to do something fun.
Sounds good.
Sasaki's last?
Yes, I'm in.
I'll do a medley of cover songs for the unit.
Oh, that's nice.
The colors of each of them came out pretty well.
A great song that fits the image of each
It could be a Christmas song or a cover of an idol's song.
or a cover of an idol's song.
There's always a quick change of clothes.
They're all working at full capacity.
That's for sure.
It's an activity.
It's better to have a project that can be done by just a few people.
It gives us a little more space.
I think it's better.
I think it would make things go more smoothly.
Fujisaki and Natsume's hysterical duo
It's okay if they are.
That's how you make up your mind.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
But isn't it a great unit?
It's okay to have a zone like that.
I don't know...
I don't know if I'll be able to make it after this.
I don't know if I'll be able to make it later, but I'd like to know who you'd like to form a unit with for the next show.
I've heard a lot of fans say that...It's something I'm often told by my fans.
Harlun and I.
I'd like to see the two of us singing a ballad or something in Haruhu.
I've had quite a few fans tell me that they'd like to see us sing a ballad together.
I'd be very happy if we could do that.
A unit is very possible, isn't it?
With Haruf's singing and the layout...
It's a torii, isn't it?
Sandwiched between shorter torii gates.
Bridge torii?
All torii.
All the torii gates.
Chicken and meat.
It's hard to find someone who goes to heaven as a loser.
They just have to make me laugh.
Do you have any ideas for a comedy act?
Go make some materials.
Materials?
Yes, sir.
But just in case... just now I heard Sakuma-san call you a coward.
Is this all wrong? Maybe...
Three of them.
Wow.
You're saying you've got three ideas?
You're bringing me three different settings?
Wow.
Does this mean they sit in a circle around Mr. Matsumoto and watch him sing?
Is that good or bad?
This is good and bad.
Oh, good, but it's December 24th, so it's like the murder of Santa Claus or something.Oh, great, but it's December 24th, so it's like Santa's murder or something.
Oh, wow.
We'll do what's on the riffraff, just for kicks and giggles, you know?
Yes, sir.
I've been thinking about that.
No, it's not that bad. It's not that bad, but it's like a 25-minute epic.
It's all very long.
Oh, and the other members, do you have any comedy?
Yes.
I've been writing them, but I'm just reading them.
I looked up "how to make a skit" and it says you have to decide on a title first.
So I decided on a title.
I like it.
Here we go.
The Chicken Escape on the Eve of Christmas
It's a bird again!
Birds are hot with the younger crowd right now.
I didn't know that.
That's why they're profiling you so much!
Me.
It's not a title anymore.
It's about a chicken with a foe, and the chicken tries to escape so it doesn't get burned.
How's that last part?
The last one ends up as a burnt chicken.
Can you sing and dance after that?
Wow!
Takanashi.
I've never thought of a comedy before, but since it's a Christmas concert...
I thought of a medium who would take a child possessed by a demon and
A medium dispels the demon.I'll pay you.
Pay me a little.
It's like Christmas.
Santa Claus is out.
I'll do my best to get him out.
Who do you think you're going to get to play a kid possessed by the devil?
Hysterical.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Fujisaki's skin?
I've been called a terrible hysteric by the members.
Hysteric Fujisaki.
Sunshine Ikezaki...
It's the entertainment industry I want to see.
R1 R1 is hysterical too.
Hysteric.
I really don't know how to be a contrarian.
That's totally fine.
You're going to present what you think is a contralto.
I looked it up like, "What's a conte?
I thought, "Well, we're a group of nine, so what do we have that's nine people?
Egyptian mythological gods.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
If you put the nine of us together...
Ra and Agris.
Great.
I like that.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
What's the title?
The Nine Pillars of Gods... The Big Family...
Olympian Gods God of Olympus.
Seriously, suddenly the Egyptian stuff is flowing.
We are
We're...
I can't do it.
This is too much.
That's so funny.
What do you think?
In Mr. Sakuma's opinion...
It'll be a Christmas party if we put it all together.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
It would be nice to have this zone.
If there was a Christmas party zone...
Christmas party is so-so
I mean the concept that wraps around the whole thing.
The first shot was really full of stuff
The second one was to show all kinds of riffraff.
But for the third one, we wanted to make it a lot of fun.
We also included the songs we've done so far with the audience's participation.
I wanted the audience to feel happy to have spent this time for Christmas.
I want the audience to be happy to have spent this time for Christmas... That's the concept.
Anyway, when you go to Ruff Ruff's live, you can't help but get excited and have fun.
I hope that the audience will be excited and have fun when they attend a Ruff Ruff concert.
I want people to feel that when they go to a Ruff Ruff concert, they will be excited and have fun.
So I guess we really want to gather the Krivochis.
I'm sure there will be a lot of "criboches" there.
I hope that they will have a live show that they will remember for the rest of their lives.
I hope that they will have a concert that they will remember for the rest of their lives.
I wish you all the best.
Yes, I'll do my best.Yes, I will do my best.
Thank you for watching.
I'm impressed that you say you have a location vehicle on location in Rough Rough Rough.
If you're going to lump us in as members, it's not us.
It's already riffraff.
I'm thrilled that there's a location car on location for Ruff Ruff.
There's a location car on location in Ruff Ruff.
Thank you for watching to the end.
Have you subscribed to our channel?
Have you clicked the good button?
Are you eating?
Are you getting any sleep?
Are there any holes in your socks?
Have you paid your bill?
Are you thinking of your hometown?
Are you happy now?
Yes, I am!